&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：问题是，你能堆叠多个
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Question is,
can you stack multiple
报头中的缓存控制策略？
cache control strategies in the header?
我的直觉说不。
My gut says no.
我也意识到我从未尝试过。
I also realize that I
have never attempted to.
所以我不能提供一个真正好的答案，但是
So I can't provide a really good answer,
but
我最初的直觉是我不认为你可以。
my initial gut says I don't think you can.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：有人测试它。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Someone test it.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：有人测试它，继续记录。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Someone test it,
keep recording.
[笑]&gt；&gt；steve kinney：还有其他问题吗？
[LAUGH]
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Any other questions?
是啊。
Yeah.
&GT；&GT；演讲者3：也许你不知道从你的头上，但是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Maybe you don't know
off the top of your head, but
只是好奇，关于发送网格或以前的项目。
just curious, on either send grid or
a previous project.
你有没有最喜欢的表演成就或者
Do you have a favorite sort of
performance accomplishment or
你脑海中浮现的任务？
task you've made that comes to mind?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我认为最重要的一个，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I think one
of the most important ones,
因为它先于所有其他指标，首先是获得指标。
cuz it precedes all other ones,
is getting the metrics in the first place.
比如弄清楚世界的状况并能让你知道这一点，
Like figuring out the state of the world
and being able to you know this,
找出这些行动，什么是重要的行动和
figuring out these actions,
what are important action and
算出他们需要多长时间，然后开始设置这些。
figuring out how long they take and
starting to set those.
要么是性能预算，对吧，如果你不想让它变得更糟，或者
Either performance budget, right,
if you don't want it to get worse, or
绩效目标。
performance goals.
这是一项非同小可的任务。
That's a nontrivial task.
试图获得这些测量，打开[INAUDIBLE]和
Trying to get those measurements,
cracking open the [INAUDIBLE] and
得到所有这些数字。
getting all those numbers.
这是第一步
It's the first step.
它通常是大多数应用程序中不存在的东西。
It's usually stuff that doesn't
exist in most applications.
耐心，对吧？
Patience, right?
就像没人做过一样，所以这不是一件事，对吧？
Like nobody's done it,
thereby it's not a thing, right?
在我的电脑上感觉很好，[笑]对吧？
Feels fine on my computer, [LAUGH] right?
是最大的事情。
Is the biggest thing.
所以喜欢继续前进，使用喜欢的用户计时API来获得一些原始的
So like going ahead and using like
the user timing API to like get some raw
数字，我觉得真的是那种喜欢的第一种。
numbers, I think is really
like the kind of like first.
因为在那之后你可以在它周围买东西，对吗？
Cuz after that you can get
the buy in around it, right?
就像，Chrome现在有一些有趣的功能，工作方式不同。
And like, Chrome has some interesting
features now, that work different.
就像他们在我的应用程序上工作得不太好，因为我们必须登录，
Like they don't work super well on
my app because we have to log in,
诸如此类的东西，但它们实际上向你展示了你的应用程序与你的竞争对手。
stuff like that but they actually show
you your app versus your competitors.
这通常有助于买进。
That's usually helpful for getting buy in.
这是一个相对较新的问题。
That's a relatively new one.
在Chrome中还有一个特别的，
There's another one in
Chrome specifically,
将向您展示代码覆盖率，对吗？
will show you code coverage, right?
这意味着它会加载你的所有代码，你点击你的应用程序，然后
Which means it'll load up all your code,
you click around your app, and
它会向您显示从未执行的代码行，对吗？
it'll show you lines of code
that were never executed, right?
所以就像开始得到这些指标，开始像这样，
And so like starting to get those metrics,
starting to get like these,
如果我有喜欢，让我们让应用程序走得更快！
if I have like,
let's make the app go faster!
感觉很棒，每个人都喜欢耶！
It's like great, everyone's like yeah!
然后什么都没发生对吧？
And then nothing happens, right?
因为就像没有一样，这是第一件要做的事，对吧？
Cuz like there's no like,
here's the first thing to do, right?
所以我认为这是最重要的部分，对吧？
So I think that's the kind of
most important part, right?
因为一旦你想把它建立到每个人都喜欢的文化中
Cuz like, once you kind of like build that
into the culture that everyone kind of
关心，完成所有这些事情变得容易多了。
cares about, it becomes a lot
easier to get all this stuff done.
在你建立它之前几乎是不可能做到的。
And it's almost impossible
to do before you build that.
所以这可能不是你要找的答案。
So it's kind of maybe not
the answer you're looking for.
但如果你问我最自豪的是什么，比如开始实施
But if you're asking what's the one I'm
proudest of, like starting to implement
这些指标和某种程度上让绩效文化就位。
those metrics and kind of getting
the culture of performance in place.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：谢谢，太好了。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Thank you, that's great.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：还有别的吗？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Anything else?
太棒了，非常感谢大家。
Cool, thank you so much, everyone.
[掌声]
[APPLAUSE]